<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Aminudin Resume</title>
    <link>http://aminudin.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Aminudin Resume</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://aminudin.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Certificates</title>
      <link>http://aminudin.me/pages/certificates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aminudin.me/pages/certificates/</guid>
      
      <description>Professional Certificates Here are my professional cybersecurity certifications that demonstrate my expertise in penetration testing and web application security.
eCPPTv3 - Certified Professional Penetration Tester Issuer: INE Security
Credential ID: 158328191
Issued: August 2025
Expires: August 2028
Verification: View Certificate
The eCPPTv3 certification demonstrates comprehensive penetration testing skills, covering:
Network penetration testing System exploitation and post-exploitation Professional penetration testing methodologies eWPTXv3 - Web Application Penetration Tester eXtreme Issuer: INE Security</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://aminudin.me/component/bio/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aminudin.me/component/bio/bio/</guid>
      
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Aminudin, a passionate Software Engineer specializing in backend development and proficient in JavaScript and TypeScript. I also have expertise in web pentesting and Android apps pentesting, with a strong commitment to security testing and vulnerability assessment.
I hold professional certifications including eWPTXv3 (eLearnSecurity Web Application Penetration Tester eXtreme) and eCPPTv3 (eLearnSecurity Certified Professional Penetration Tester), demonstrating my advanced skills in cybersecurity and penetration testing.
I enjoy coding and exploring new technologies to build secure and efficient solutions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://aminudin.me/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aminudin.me/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
